{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_Chertoff",
    "predicate": "property/appointer",
    "object": "resource/George_W._Bush",
    "human_readable": "Michael Chertoff was appointed by George W. Bush.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9626096487045288,
            "question": "What is the significance of Michael Chertoff's appointment by George W. Bush?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9208404421806335,
            "question": "During whose presidency was Michael Chertoff appointed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9163011908531189,
            "question": "Who appointed Michael Chertoff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8813077807426453,
            "question": "What position was Michael Chertoff appointed to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7579755783081055,
            "question": "What were some of Michael Chertoff's responsibilities in his appointed role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7176560759544373,
            "question": "How did Michael Chertoff's background prepare him for his appointed role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.662256121635437,
            "question": "Were there any controversies surrounding Michael Chertoff's appointment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5361539125442505,
            "question": "Was Michael Chertoff involved in any significant events during his time in office?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3560500741004944,
            "question": "Who is George W. Bush?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2076854556798935,
            "question": "What political party was George W. Bush affiliated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Chertoff was appointed by George W. Bush.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7355_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is George W. Bush?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7355_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Michael Chertoff involved in any significant events during his time in office?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7355_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any controversies surrounding Michael Chertoff's appointment?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7355_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7355_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7355_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7355_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7355_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7355_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7355_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7355_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7355_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7355_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7355_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`\n\nThe documents mention that Michael Chertoff was nominated and later unanimously approved as Secretary of Homeland Security under President George W. Bush, which implies that he was indeed appointed by George W. Bush."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Michael Chertoff was nominated and approved as the Secretary of Homeland Security under President George W. Bush, which supports the statement that he was appointed (nominated and confirmed) by George W. Bush."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context information states Chertoff was appointed by George H. W. Bush, not George W. Bush.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}